Hey, welcome back. This video is
specifically for Macs. Uh specifically,
if you are planning to use Safari, um
now that you've built your first HTML
page, you are officially a web
developer. So, it's time to change some
settings. So, on your Safari, navigate
up to the top bar, click on Safari,
click settings, and it'll pop up this
window. We're going to come all the way
over here and click advanced. So, it
probably brought you to the general tab.
We are going to come over here to the
advanced tab and then down here at the
bottom it says show features for web
developers. You're going to want to
click that button. You are now a web
developer. This is a big step for you.
So go ahead and click that button. And
as soon as you've done that, you can
click X. You know it works. If you can
click here and click inspect, if you can
rightclick and click inspect element,
that means you have successfully done
your job. We'll talk more about this in
the next video, but on a Mac, there's
some extra steps you need to take. So, I
just wanted to make this video for you.
I hope that helps.